fridaymoviez.com 2014-04-07

# Twilight Entertainment Private Ltd : Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. By accepting our Privacy Policy, you consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner prescribed in this Privacy Policy. 

**Information - Collection, Sharing and Disclosure**  
Our primary aim in collecting information is to provide and improve our services, features and content, to administer your membership and to enable you to enjoy and further facilitate you in relishing the premium quality digital experience  brought to you by FRIDAYMOVIEZ.COM.  
Your IP address is used in diagnosing problems with our server and administering our website and services. Through our surveys, subscriptions, and registrations, we request users to give us contact, demographic and/or financial information (like name, locale, gender, age, income level and email address) so that we could enhance our user experience by being more content specific. The contact information is used to notify users of new services and content, as well as for surveys and newsletters. Our site may use an order form for customers to subscribe to our for-pay services. We collect contact information (like e-mail address) and financial information (like account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send billing invoices. 

Contact information is also used to get in touch with the subscribers when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future communications by unsubscribing. Financial information that is collected is used, among other things, to bill the user for products and services for in-house statistics, advertising, and marketing target information. We do not share personal financial information with any other parties without your consent. Information collected during registration is used for in-house statistics and marketing target information. This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites or any website from which you may have linked to us. We are committed to protecting your privacy online. We collect certain personal information in order to provide you with customized services, content, and advertisements. We may disclose to third parties certain aggregate information only when such action is reasonably necessary to comply with the law, legal process, or to enforce the terms of service. 

We will also use your personal information for the purposes of providing you with any services to which you subscribe, service-related activities and notifying you or contacting you regarding any problem with, or the expiration of, such services. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. We will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. Also remember to sign out of your account and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe. This privacy policy is not intended to, and does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of us. 

**Children**   
We encourage parents to take an active role in their children's use of the Internet, and to inform them of the dangers of providing information about themselves over the Internet. Children of any age should always ask a parent for permission before sending personal information to anyone online. No information should be submitted to or posted on this web site by users under 18 years of age without the consent of their parent or guardian. Children are not eligible to use our services and we ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor, you can use this service only in conjunction with your parents or guardians. 

**Advertisements**

Ads appearing on this web site are delivered to you by either our web advertising partners or by us. Information about your visit to this site, such as the number of times you have viewed an ad, your browser type, the type of computer operating system you use and whether or not you responded to the ad delivered, (but not your name, address, phone number or other personal information), is used to serve advertisements to you on this site. We may use your zip code or geographical location information to serve advertisements to this site. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. We aggregate personally identifiable information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for other marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you personally. Certain information, such as your name, email address, password, credit card number, and bank account number, are never disclosed to marketing advertisers. This site may use its own proprietary ad serving system and may allow for third party ad serving systems, all approved at the site's discretion. The site and its third party servers collect and store anonymous data, typically through the use of cookies. 

**Security**

We take great care to insure that your private information is as safe as possible through the use of secure technology and internal processes. As an example, any information that we collect about you is stored in an access-controlled environment, preventing access by unauthorized people. Also, any time your information is passed across the Internet, it is protected by the use of encryption technology. Your account is also password protected, and allows you to modify or update your information at any time. 

**Contacting the Website**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact:   
FRIDAYMOVIEZ.COM ****  
**TWILIGHT ENTERTAINMENT PVT LTD**  
#204 / A, Kamanwala Chambers,   
Moghul Lane,   
Mahim (W),   
Mumbai - 16  
T: + 91 22 4347 1818/19  
F: + 91 22 4347 1820
